{
    "subject": "resource/Viewbank_College",
    "predicate": "property/country",
    "object": "resource/Australia",
    "human_readable": "Viewbank College is located in Australia.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8869336843490601,
            "question": "Where is Viewbank College located?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8123614192008972,
            "question": "In what country is Viewbank College situated?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.603439450263977,
            "question": "What type of institution is Viewbank College?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5357397794723511,
            "question": "What continent is Viewbank College on?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.41637447476387024,
            "question": "Is Viewbank College an international school?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3572814464569092,
            "question": "Is Viewbank College known for its community involvement?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.30462220311164856,
            "question": "Does Viewbank College offer a range of academic programs?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2983742952346802,
            "question": "Are there any notable alumni from Viewbank College?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2828274071216583,
            "question": "What are some extracurricular activities offered at Viewbank College?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.1902410387992859,
            "question": "Does Viewbank College have a strong emphasis on sports and athletics?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Viewbank College is located in Australia.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7281_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some extracurricular activities offered at Viewbank College?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7281_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any notable alumni from Viewbank College?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7281_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Does Viewbank College offer a range of academic programs?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7281_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7281_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7281_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7281_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7281_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7281_42.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7281_48.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7281_74.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7281_78.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7281_79.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7281_90.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the structured JSON response:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports the triple that Viewbank College is located in Australia. The documents mention the college's location in the northern suburb of Rosanna and its presence in Melbourne, which is a city in Australia."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe information provided in the documents supports that Viewbank College is an Australian public secondary school, which confirms its location in Australia."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}